brightside.me 2018-12-26

# Privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

Last updated on 25 May, 2018 

Welcome to the Privacy Policy of *Bright Side. The privacy of our website visitors is very important to us, and we are committed to safeguarding it. This policy explains what we will do with your personal information. 

_*Bright Side (« _our Website_ ») is owned and operated by ADME (CY) LTD (« _we_ », « _us_ », or « _our_ »). _

### 1\. Types of Personal Information That Might Be Collected

When you visit our Website, the following types of *Personally Identifiable Information (as such term is explained at the end of this Section) about you may be collected: 

  * your IP address;
  * your operating system and browser software used to access our Website;
  * other information, as will be explained in Section 4 ( _With Whom We  Share Information_) below;   
and
  * in the event you contact us by email, we may keep a record of that correspondence; such record may include, apart from your email address, the Personally Identifiable Information that you will include in the communication.

Such data are collected by Our Partners (as such term is explained in Section 4).

If you wish to register on our Website in order to receive our subscription-based services, we will ask you to provide the following data:

  * your email address;
  * your gender;   
and
  * your date of birth.

In addition, when subscribing for any of the services offered on our Website you will be requested to identify your display name and choose your profile image which may be an avatar or a photo. The display name is what will be displayed next to your comments on our Website. We strongly encourage you not to use your real-life name and/or surname as your display name. 

We never share with third parties any of the data supplied by you as part of subscription-based services/registration. 

### 2\. Ways Personal Information Might Be Used

_Use of  Personal Data by Us._ We collect and use your Personally Identifiable Information for the following legitimate business purposes of ADME (CY) LTD and the group of companies to which it belongs: 

  * to carry out general data analysis and to administer our Website and affiliated sites;
  * to generate statistics and measure web traffic and popularity of specific areas of our Website;
  * to identify usage trends and expand our business activities;
  * to build higher quality and develop more useful services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our users
  * to improve or modify our Website, develop new services and functionality;
  * to comply with applicable legal requirements, legal process and relevant industry standards, and satisfy requests by governmental and supervisory authorities;   
and
  * to identify and prevent fraud.

Additionally, if you choose to register on our Website in order to receive our subscription-based services, your Personally Identifiable Information will be used in order to communicate with you. 

If, at any time, you decide to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, detailed unsubscribe instructions will be displayed at the bottom of each email. 

_Use of  Personal Data by Our Partners._ Our Partners (as such term is explained in Section 4, With Whom We Share Information) may be collecting and using your Personally Identifiable Information to tailor the content that advertisers display to you, including building relevant data segments based on what you click and view and when or how many times you have viewed it; for these purposes, they use the information collected by technologies, such as pixel tags or cookies, to improve the services provided by third-party advertising companies, which include Google. The list of Google partners can be viewed at partners. 

### 3\. What You Agree to by Using Our Website

We will ask for your consent and agreement that we may collect and use your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and as permitted or required by law. You are free to refuse to give consent or to withdraw the consent that you had given. Please note, however, that if you refuse or withdraw your consent some of the features available on our Website may not be available to you. Please note that we may also rely on legitimate interests or fulfillment of a contract to continue processing your Personally Identifiable Information. **Consent can be  withdrawn at any time by navigating to consent and clicking the box to remove consent.**

Please understand that, if you decide to register on our Website in order to receive our subscription-based services, by submitting any Personally Identifiable Information to us, you are giving consent and agreeing that we may collect and use all Personally Identifiable Information that you submit in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted or required by law. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not provide any Personally Identifiable Information to us. 

Before using Personally Identifiable Information for a purpose other than any of the purposes set out in the preceding Section 2 (Ways Personal Information Might Be Used) we will request your explicit consent. 

### 4\. With Whom We Share Information

Except as set forth in this Policy or as explicitly agreed by you, **we  will not disclose any of your Personally Identifiable Information.** In addition to the other uses set forth in this Policy, we may disclose and otherwise use Personally Identifiable Information as described below. 

_Our Partners._ We allow third parties, including carefully selected ad networks and business partners (referred to as « _Our Partners_ »), to display advertising on our Website. Our Partners may, for instance, collect, use and share your information to make or help us make predictions about your interests, and may provide you with offers, promotional materials, and advertisements. In addition, Our Partners may be collecting certain information related to your PC, laptop, mobile phone or other device attributes and traffic/session information. Our Website permits Our Partners to collect your Personally Identifiable Information to provide personalized advertising to you. Our Partners are leading digital performance-based advertising groups which put great effort in making sure that your personal information is safe and used properly. 

_Service Providers._ Your information may be collected by entities that provide services to us, including companies that deliver web analytics, data processing, data enhancement and customer insights, advertising, email distribution, and other services. 

_Other Parties (when required by  law or as necessary to protect our services)._ We may disclose your information (including Personally Identifiable Information) to other parties in order to: 

  * protect our legal rights or property, the legal rights or property of our affiliates, and sites or services we work with;
  * protect the rights, safety and security of our users, ourselves, or any other person or entity;
  * prevent fraud (or for risk management purposes);   
or
  * comply with applicable legal requirements, legal process or request for cooperation by a governmental or supervisory authority, whether or not legally required. For example, we may be required to disclose your information to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

_Other Parties (in  connection with transfer of assets)._ If we make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or transfer (or due diligence related to such a transaction), or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, we may transfer your Personally Identifiable Information as part of that transaction. 

_Use for Analytical and Ad  Serving Purposes._ We use standard tools common within the industry, such as Google Analytics, to collect information about use of our Website. These tools collect information such as how often you visit our Website and what other sites you visited prior to reaching our Website. We use the information we obtain from analytical tools for the purposes of improving our Website. The analytical tools collect only the IP address assigned to your computer or other device and your browser settings as of the moment you visit our Website, rather than your name or other identifying information. 

We also use standard tools common within the industry, such as DoubleClick for Publishers operated by Google, enabling placement and management of personalized advertising services on our Website. These tools use cookies to target advertising based on what is relevant to you as a user to improve advertising and to avoid showing ads that you have already seen. Cookies themselves contain no Personally Identifiable Information. They relate to your web activity, rather than your identity. Tools such as DoubleClick will send a cookie to your web browser after any impression, click, or other activity by you on our servers. If your web browser accepts the cookie, the cookie will be planted on your web browser. DoubleClick will usually send a cookie to your web browser when you visit any webpage displaying DoubleClick ads. Webpages containing DoubleClick ads include ad tags that instruct web browsers to request ad content from our servers. When the server delivers the ad content, it will also send a cookie. 

Finally, our Website relies on common industry tools Google Display Network Impression Reporting and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. These tools help us understand the composition of viewers of our Website in terms of gender, age and interests. We need this information in order to understand what types of creative content we need to develop to suit the interests of different demographic and interest groups. In addition, Our Partners may need this information to develop marketing content. You may, at any time, opt out of Google Analytics tracking, including Google Display Network Impression Reporting and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, by installing the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). You may also opt out of ad serving through [Google’s opt-out page](https://adssettings.google.com/u/0/authenticated). 

The personal data privacy aspects of all Google products, services and features, including Google Analytics and DoubleClick, are covered by [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Please be assured that we never combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics or DoubleClick with any other Personally Identifiable Information. Moreover, permanent cookies planted on your web browser by Google products to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our Website, cannot be used by anyone but Google. The ability of Google to use and share information collected by Google Analytics or DoubleClick about your visits to our Website is restricted by [DoubleClick Terms and Conditions](https://www.google.com/intl/en_ALL/doubleclick/tos/dfp-api-terms.html), [Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). 

You can opt out of ads personalization using Google’s Ads Settings by following the instructions contained on the following resource of Google — [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). If you choose to opt out of ads personalization, you will no longer receive personalized advertising. 

### 5\. Cross-Border Transfer of Information

We generally maintain centralized servers and systems in Europe and may maintain servers and systems elsewhere. These servers and systems are managed by us or on our behalf, or by our affiliates located in Europe. 

In the event of transfer and processing of your Personally Identifiable Information outside the EEA for the purposes described above, we will ascertain that the information receives the same level of protection as if it remained within the EEA, including when entering into data transfer agreements, using the EU Commission approved Standard Contractual Clauses, or by relying on certification schemes such as the EU-US Privacy Shield. 

### 6\. How We Keep Your Information Secure

We use commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your Personally Identifiable Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction in accordance with requirements of applicable laws. 

### 7\. Use of ‘Cookies’

We also use (or may use) ‘cookies’ when you visit our Website. For more information on our use of cookies, please refer to our Cookie Policy. 

### 8\. Use of Information for Personal Advertising

The information collected by Our Partners is used to analyze trends, understand user activities and gather demographic information to enable, manage and develop their personalized ads and related services. Our Partners may share such information with their affiliates. To do this, Our Partners use technologies such as cookies and web beacons to collect information about your interaction with our Website and third-party websites. This type of information does not identify you personally and, typically, is aggregated with other data to create segments —groups of users and general interest categories that are inferred based on a range of factors (for example, «sports fan»). Our Partners use this information to form a more accurate picture of the interests of the audiences with which they interact — including you — so that their ads are more relevant to those interests. 

In addition, Our Partners may use the information collected from these types of cookie or similar technologies for a variety of other purposes, including: 

  * in conjunction with advertising that appears on other third-party websites;
  * to measure the effectiveness of web-based and email advertisements;   
and
  * for reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement data and other interaction with ads and the websites on which they are served.

Our Partners retain your information in accordance with their legitimate business purposes for processing. Thereafter, the information is removed, archived for restricted legitimate interests, or anonymized. Non-identifying information may be kept without time and use limitations. 

### 9\. Retention of Personal Information

If you reside or are located in the EEA, your Personally Identifiable Information will be stored for no longer than necessary for the purpose for which the Personally Identifiable Information was collected. The length of time Personally Identifiable Information is retained depends on the purpose for which such information was collected and/or as required to comply with applicable laws and establish, exercise or defend our legal rights. 

### 10\. Your Legal Rights

You have certain rights in relation to your Personally Identifiable Information. Depending on the jurisdiction, you have the right to request that we: 

  * provide access to any Personally Identifiable Information we, or Our Partners, hold about you;
  * update any Personally Identifiable Information which is out of date or incorrect;
  * delete any Personally Identifiable Information which we, or Our Partners, are holding about you;
  * object to certain means of processing of Personally Identifiable Information (e.g., opt-out from marketing communications);
  * restrict the way in which we process your Personally Identifiable Information;
  * provide your Personally Identifiable Information to a third-party service provider;   
or
  * provide you with a copy of any Personally Identifiable Information which we hold about you.

### 11\. Children’s Privacy

No part of our Website is directed to children or minors under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from anyone that we know is under 18 years of age. If you are under 16 years of age (unless a lower age threshold between 13 and 16 applies in your country), then please do not use or access this Website, or ask your parents for permission before using our Website or sending any information about yourself to anyone over the Internet. We will take appropriate steps to delete any Personally Identifiable Information of persons less than 13 years of age that has been collected on our Website without verifiable parental consent upon learning of the existence of such Personally Identifiable Information. 

### 12\. Questions, Suggestions and Complaints

If you have any privacy-related questions, suggestions, unresolved problems, or complaints you may contact us at [legalops@thesoul-publishing.com](mailto:legalops@thesoul-publishing.com). 

If you reside or are located within the EEA, we may assist with all queries regarding our processing of Personally Identifiable Information. We request that you please attempt to resolve any issues related to your Personally Identifiable Information with us first. If you reside or are located within the EEA, you may also make a complaint to the supervisory authority for data protection in your country of residence (such as, for instance, the UK Information Commissioner’s Office for the UK) or seek a remedy through local courts if you believe that your rights have been breached. 

### 13\. External Links

Our Website may display links to websites of third-party content providers, other than Our Partners. We do not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties, other than Our Partners, without obtaining your consent specifically permitting such disclosure. We do not endorse and are not responsible for the privacy practices and content of such third parties. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to understand how they collect and process your Personally Identifiable Information. 

### 14\. Changes to This Policy

We revise and evaluate this Policy periodically in light of changing business practices, technology and legal requirements. As a result, this Policy will be updated from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. Any change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on our Website. 

### 15\. Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Policy, our privacy practices, or to exercise your rights, please contact us by email at [legalops@thesoul-publishing.com](mailto:legalops@thesoul-publishing.com). You also may contact us by sending a letter or request to: 

General Counsel  
ADME (CY) LTD  
Office 102, 28th Oktovriou Str. 359  
Limassol 3107, Cyprus
